I'm going to appear in a TV commercial
for Abe-Katsu Motors.
Abe-Katsu is a big company.
I knew it.
That's it.
Good morning.
It's a nice day.
I'm going to show my inner self.
I've been thinking that many people
know about you.
What kind of episode is it?
I'm curious.
You want to be filmed?
No, no.
I've seen you, but I've never heard of
you.
I've only seen you on the escalator at
Sendai Station.
I haven't been doing my best.
I'm going to ask people if they know
you.
What?
Is it a general question?
I want to verify a theory.
If you're asked if you know about me,
I'm in a car commercial with ABEKATSU.
I see.
I'm told.
I'm also in a car commercial with
ABEKATSU.
Do you think I'm doing something?
I'm in a car commercial with ABEKATSU.
I see.
I'm going to verify a theory.
Interesting.
I've seen you, but I've never heard of
you.
I'm going to tell you.
It's like a commentator.
I'm going to increase the number of
viewers.
I'm going to make a board before I
leave.
I see.
I'm going to answer if you know me or
not.
I see.
I'm going to make a board and leave
when it's done.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm going to make a board.
Let's get started.
I'm going to tell you what you need.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to tell you what people say.
I smell good.
I see.
You don't have to say anything.
I'm going to tell you what people say.
I'm going to make a board.
Let's get started.
I'm going to tell you what people say.
I'm going to make a board.
I can do it!
No, it's not a car.
It's the east.
I can do it!
I saw it from a distance.
I'm scared.
I can't believe it's not a bear.
It's a bear with a square face.
What is it?
It's a bear with a straight neck.
No!
I hit a child.
What's wrong with you?
Are you OK?
I don't know.
I'll ask a professional painter.
I can't do it.
The eyes are facing down.
It's up.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm a little bit worried about the
angle.
Great!
Thank you.
Amazing.
It's done.
There is a CD.
Oh, yes.
It's a CD of Hinari Toku.
Please listen to it.
Thank you.
I'm nervous.
I'm a little bit nervous.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to go.
Please look forward to the next video!
I came to the park.
There are a lot of people because it's
a child's season, so I think I'll ask
for a voice.
Let's do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm shooting a video, but is it okay to
shoot?
Thank you.
Do you know Tomiki Igeyani?
Yes, I do.
What did you know about her?
She is a student of the same age as me.
She lives in Tokyo.
I'm glad to hear that.
Congratulations!
This is the first time to celebrate.
Thank you.
Congratulations!
I'm sorry I'm late.
Thank you.
Do you know Tomoki Igeyani?
I don't know.
Do you know her?
I know her.
I've seen her on TV.
I've heard her name.
I don't know her.
She is in a commercial called Abe-Katsu
Jidou-Cha.
Do you know her?
I know her.
Thank you.
They are the ones who made this CD.
This is our CD.
Please check it out.
Thank you.
Do you know Tomomi Igeyani?
Yes, I do.
What did you know about her?
I've heard her on a video of Youtube
called Whatever.
I thought it was a great song.
I'm glad to hear that.
What did you like about her?
I liked Hinjyu Kichijo.
I knew her because of that.
How old is she?
She is 18 years old.
She is not a new member.
Is she in a serious relationship?
Please sign your CD.
Thank you.
Do you know her?
I've seen her on a video of Youtube
called Whatever.
I'm glad to hear that.
She is cute.
Other girls are cute, too.
Thank you.
I enjoyed it.
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you know Igeyani Tanaka?
I know her.
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you know her?
I'm sorry.
She is a member of Shonen Naka.
I've heard her on a video of Adekatsu
Gidousha.
Nara Go-Occupy.
I've heard that.
I've heard that, too.
I like her.
I've seen her on a video of Youtube
called Whatever.
I've heard that.
It's a season of meeting.
I'm glad to hear that.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
I was doing street interview.
I was asked if I knew you.
Of course.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
What made you know me?
I knew you since you appeared on TV.
I was a TV commercial model.
I was a model for a station.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad to hear that you are going to
hold a live show.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Me, too.
You are beautiful.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you for your rap.
I was doing street interview.
I was asked if I knew you.
Of course.
I was a model for a station.
I'm glad to hear that.
What did you come here for?
I came here for a lunch.
That's good.
I was told that you were a model for a
station.
That's good.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
Please watch the show on YouTube.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm a
fan of
Atsushi Abe
I'm a fan of
Haruto Kikuno
Thank you
I'm a fan of
Ratsuta Otomone
Thank you
Who are you?
This is a report
It's a report
Wow
It's effective
I didn't know that
13 people knew
Many people don't know
Yes
But you know a lot about Atsushi Abe
3 people don't know
I'm a fan of
Atsushi Abe
Thank you
Let's go home
Please subscribe us!
YUKARI!!!!
I'm going to check the ticket now.
Do you have a ticket to go to Itohoku?
No, I don't.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to join the game of Amekatsu
Automobile.
Amekatsu No.1!
I know it!
Wow!
Thank you very much.
I got the ticket.
Here is your ticket.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Here is your ticket.
Thank you very much.
Please take it.
Please check our YouTube channel.
We are waiting for your comment.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I came to the main hall of Itohoku in
Itohoku.
What is the activity?
I came to the game of Amekatsu
Automobile.
Here is your ticket.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
You are very beautiful.
I'm from the same school as you.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad I'm here.
Thank you.
I'm doing a survey on YouTube.
Do you know who Iginori Tohoku is?
I don't know.
I'm a fan of a commercial of Abekatsu
Automobile.
I'm a fan of Abekatsu Nagano.
I finally understand.
Thank you.
I heard about you.
I'm the president of the district.
I'm not the president of the district.
I'm the chairman of the Shinko Kumiai.
Please listen to my story.
That's good.
I'm glad to hear that.
Thank you.
Don't bury me.
Don't bury me here.
Thank you.
There is a beautiful park in the
district.
The district is producing rice for the
rice field.
I'm collaborating with Onagawa.
I'm going to plant rice with yuzu.
I like yuzu.
It takes time to grow it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Please enjoy the district.
Thank you.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll be there.
Thank you.
Please come to the district.
I love you.
Thank you.
I'm a fan of a commercial of Abekatsu
Automobile.
I know a lot of people.
I know a lot of people who know
Abekatsu Automobile.
It's a rich story.
We were surprised.
If we go to the district, more people
will know us.
That's right.
Because everyone received our CDs.
I'm glad.
No one refused.
I want to continue my activities.
Please do it.
I want to do it on Takeshita Street in
Harajuku.
No one knows it.
Only Miyagi knows it.
Please tell me the number of people you
know and don't know.
I know.
There are 14 people.
What about people you don't know?
There are 44 people.
There are many people you don't know.
But, I think everyone knows about
Abekatsu Automobile.
I love the fireworks.
I want to go home with fireworks.
But, we have a schedule after this.
So, we will go home.
I'm glad that we don't have a CD.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
Can you watch our videos on YouTube?
Yes, we can.
Did you watch our videos?
Yes, we did.
Please give us a high rating.
Please subscribe to our channel.
Please check our Twitter.
We have Instagram and TikTok.
We will post all the links.
Please check them.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching this video.
Please subscribe to this channel.
Please follow us on Twitter and
Instagram.
Please follow our official Twitter and